♪ Men. ♪
Can I ask you
a personal question?
No, Jake, I've never
measured my penis.
No, it's not about that.
I heard my dad say you're
worth like a billion dollars.
You know, I'm not
really comfortable
talking about my
financial situation.
Oh, okay.
Let's just say I'd have
more money than God,
if God only had 900 million.
Wow! You don't have any kids,
do you?
- Nope.
- Here, let me push the cart.
Thanks. So if you have
so much money,
why do you do your
own grocery shopping?
I mean, you could
just write a list
and hire someone
to do it for you.
You know, like a
17-year-old go-getter
with a valid driver's license
and no chance at
getting into college?
Well, I could, but you know,
since I've been single
I find I really like
shopping for myself.
You're kidding. Why?
Well, take this, for example.
"Baco-berries." How could
I put this on a list?
I didn't even
know it existed.
I don't even know
what it is.
What is it, anyway?
"Delicious dried cranberries
infused with real bacon flavor""
Ugh, that's disgusting.
So... do you have a bunch of
houses and yachts and stuff?
Two houses, no yachts.
You should totally get a yacht,
and then hire someone
to drive it for you.
You know, like
a 17-year-old go-getter
with a valid yacht
driver's license.
Ah, yachts are pretentious.
I don't believe in ostentatious
displays of wealth.
Besides, if I need
to get anywhere,
I'll just take my private jet.
You have a jet?
Yeah, and I already got
a go-getter pilot.
With a college degree.
Excuse me, do you know
the difference
between "organic beef"
and "grass-fed beef"?
Yeah, "organic" is, uh, no
antibiotics or growth hormones,
but it can still be
force-fed grain, which produces
a less nutritious product
than cows that are allowed
to naturally graze on grass.
Speaking of which,
you're very pretty,
and your accent makes me
feel tingly inside.
Speaking of which...?
Cows, meat, cuts of steak,
London Broil, England,
your accent,
'ello!
- Hello. I'm Zoey.
- Walden.
Nice to meet you, Walden.
Your accent's rather
charming, as well.
Thanks.
Good luck with your meat.
And they call me Forrest Gump.
What?
She was totally hitting on you.
Really?
You should ask her out.
Okay.
Hey, Zoey, you want to
go on a date with me?
Sure!
See, there's something else
I wouldn't know to
put on the list.
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x10 ♪
A Fishbowl Full of Glass Eyes
Original Air Date on November 21, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪
Okay...
I can pay the Mastercard
with the Visa,
and the Visa
with the Discover card,
and the Discover with
the American Express...
Now what can I use to complete
my little Ponzi scheme?
Chevron? No.
Blockbuster? They're in
worse shape than I am.
Starbucks gift card.
Ooh, hello latte!
- Hey.
Oh, I know that game--
"Seven Card Screwed."
If I could just get
a little ahead, I'd be fine.
And if I could just
lose a little weight,
I'd be a swimsuit model.
Go ahead, say something,
I dare you.
Oh, no, no.
It's an apt comparison.
They both involve
losing your ass.
Well, I hate to do it,
but I-I could ask Walden
for a short-term loan.
For God's sakes, Zippy,
the man is already
letting you and your kid
live here rent-free.
Don't you have
any pride at all?
Let me say that another way.
Why do you think he's
letting you stay here?
Because he likes me.
Because he likes having at
least one person in his life
that doesn't want
anything from him.
Somebody he thinks
cares about him as a person.
That's a good point.
What you don't
want him to find out
is that you're just one of
those nasty little birds
that picks the food
out of a hippo's teeth.
No, we don't want that.
So, listen, uh...
I suppose, over the years,
you've salted away
a pretty good nest egg.
You're not going to
ask me for money.
No, no! Just making
conversation.
Thanks for bringing in
my groceries, man.
I live to serve.
Boy, I gotta
tell you, Alan,
your son made one heck of
a wingman today.
You make it easy, boss.
Baby bird doesn't fly far
from the teeth.
So you, uh, you met somebody?
Indeed I did.
Beautiful woman. British.
Actually drove her shopping cart
on the wrong side of the aisle.
That's a lot of credit cards.
Uh, yeah.
I've only got this
one black one.
I actually bought
my plane with it.
Oh, oh, oh!
Which reminds me.
Hey Jake, you want
a quarter of a million
frequent flyer miles? I can't
use 'em, I got a plane.
I want a quarter of
a million anything.
All yours, my man.
Hmm, where could I go that's a
quarter of a million miles away?
How about the moon?
That's ridiculous, Dad.
I know, I was kidding.
No one's ever been to the moon.
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go.
State of the art.
And semi-portable.
Gateway computer.
I haven't seen one
of these in a while.
Still works great. And it
is loaded with software.
Quicken 95, Lotus 1-2-3...
um... WordPerfect, Tetris.
I don't know, pal.
I don't think I can move this.
Oh, come on, help me out,
I'm desperate.
As opposed to most of
the people who come in here.
In my storeroom, I've got
a couple of wheelchairs,
a fishbowl full of glass eyes,
and a "boy in the bubble" bag.
To be clear, they took
the boy out of the bubble
and sold me the bag.
Um...
Uh, what would you give me for
a pair of diamond cufflinks?
Oh...
Where'd you get these?
My mother gave them to me
when I graduated college.
- Is she your real mother?
- Yeah. Why?
'Cause these aren't
real diamonds.
What?!
I'm sure she was a good
mother in other ways.
No, this is the nicest thing
she ever did for me.
I'm very sorry.
All right. All right. I didn't
want to have to sell this,
but, uh, I suppose
I'm out of options.
Ooh.
Oh, nice.
Steuben crystal, huh?
It is.
Your mother didn't
give you this.
No. It was a wedding gift
from my wife's parents.
I managed to sneak it out of
the house after the divorce.
Uh-huh. Well, gimme a sec.
I'll give you $1,200.
Yes!
No!
I'll give you $2.00
to clean it up.
Where's your broom?
♪ Men. ♪
Jake, I'm ready to go!
Coming!
Here you go, sir.
The car is charged, washed,
and I put an air freshener
under your seat
just in case you
let one slip out.
Good job.
Hundred bucks! Thanks, boss.
You gave him $100?
Oh, hey, Alan.
Yeah, he washed my car.
A hundred bucks
to wash a car?
Not enough?
For $100,
I'd lick your car clean.
Maybe next time.
Hey, I'm going on
a date with that girl
I met in at supermarket.
Do I look okay?
No, I look okay.
You look like the guy
women fantasize about
when I'm on top of them.
Listen, I-I know you're still
pretty new to the dating world,
but can I give you
a little advice?
Is this about condoms?
'Cause Jake already
gave me his lucky one.
No. Uh...
If you hope to have any
kind of shot with this woman,
you, uh, might want to
lose the wedding ring.
Really?
Oh yeah.
When it comes to dating,
wedding rings are
like kryptonite.
If, you know,
Superman was a... vagina.
You know, I haven't
taken this off in years.
When Bridget and I first got
together, we were pretty broke,
so we just exchanged
these cheap bands,
but then, after I made my first
million, I got matching ones
made out of rhodium
and platinum.
In retrospect, I should've had
them made out of poop and tears.
Wait, uh... what's rhodium?
It's the most expensive
metal in the world.
To symbolize how precious
our love was.
Well, that's... very romantic.
But again, it's Lex Luthor
for lady parts.
Boy...
This is gonna be tough.
Wearing it makes me feel...
secure.
Be that as it may,
you have a choice to make.
Either the past,
or the future.
The memory of Bridget,
or the promise of...
supermarket strange.
- Here.
- Why are you giving it to me?
Because you're right.
I've got to
move on with my life.
And this ring is just an anchor
chaining me to the past.
Thanks, Al.
Well, you are very welcome.
Enjoy your date!
Will do. See you.
My precious!
♪ Men. ♪
So the young man you were
with at the supermarket
is no relation to you?
Oh, no, Jake...
Mm.
is Alan's son.
And Alan is...?
Uh, it's complicated.
I'm fairly bright, try me.
Okay.
Um, when I tried to kill
myself in the ocean,
Alan's house was
the closest one with a phone.
I see.
- You don't, do you?
- Not at all.
- Okay, let me back up.
- Please do.
Okay, when I was in high school,
I met this girl named Bridget.
Is it really necessary to
back up quite that far?
You're right, I'll skip ahead.
Let's see... I got married
right after high school,
happy, happy, happy.
Made like a billion dollars,
rich, rich, rich.
She decided she didn't
want to be married anymore,
sad, sad, sad.
In the ocean,
out of the ocean,
bought Alan's house, got rid
of the furniture, kept Alan,
got hungry, went to the
supermarket, met you. The end.
Wow.
Enough about me.
Let's talk about you.
No, no, I have a few
follow-up questions.
The furniture?
The suicide.
Oh, it was just a cry
for attention.
I wanted Bridget
to feel sorry for me.
Well, that's rather pathetic.
In hindsight, yeah.
And the billion dollars?
I sold a couple companies
to Microsoft.
Big mistake.
Oh, you regret it?
No, they do.
How long's it been
since your wife left?
Four months, three weeks,
four days, six hours and change.
Let's just call it six hours.
You're still in love
with her, aren't you?
You really are bright.
I thought it was
just your accent.
It kind of raises
the question,
"Why on Earth did
you ask me out""
Jake told me to.
Alan's son.
Yeah, and also wanted to because
I'm moving on with my life.
See? Look, no wedding ring.
Mmm, I noticed the
bright white tan line.
Yeah, it's almost like
I still got it on.
It is.
No worries. I gave it to Alan.
The man you kept
instead of furniture.
Well, it wasn't an either/or.
What about you?
What's your deal?
My deal.
All right, I'm a lawyer.
Ugh! Ech!
What else?
Well, I'm divorced and I have
a five-year-old daughter, Ava.
I always wanted to have kids,
but Bridget insisted
that we already had one.
I don't follow.
Me.
Oh, sure, I can see that.
What do you think?
Are we gonna fall in love
and stuff?
What?
'Cause that would really teach
Bridget a lesson.
Hi, again.
Oy gevalt.
I, uh, brought something
else for you.
My sphincter's tight
with anticipation.
Platinum and rhodium.
Whoa.
Oh...
very valuable.
Did you steal it?
What?
I'm only asking because it
affects my marketing strategy.
No, it was a gift.
A gift.
Mmm-hmm.
Heh. Good enough for me.
What are you
looking to get for it?
Let's not play this game.
Just... just tell me
what it's worth to you.
What is this,
your phone number?
That's my offer.
Hang on a sec.
You know that's helium?
Hmm?
A down-on-his-luck
birthday clown.
Son of a bitch!
♪ Men. ♪
This was a lovely
evening, Walden.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hmm. Well, better
get in, let Ava's
babysitter go home.
Oh, is she still up?
Can I meet her?
I'm sure she's still up,
but no.
Oh, I get it.
You want to know make
sure a guy's gonna be
around a while before
you introduce him-- me.
Exactly.
So, maybe after the third
or fourth date?
I don't think so.
Well, the fifth or sixth?
No.
Seventh or eighth?
I'm starting
to get a bad feeling.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You seem
like a really sweet guy,
but I think you're still kind
of married to your Bridget.
No, no, I'm not.
I haven't been wearing
my ring for, like,
like, almost three hours now.
It may be off your finger,
but it's still in your head.
Face it, you're not
ready to be dating yet.
Thanks again for dinner.
Still married.
That is so untrue.
Bridget, you're not gonna
believe what just happened.
♪ Men. ♪
Walden?
Walden?!
Down here!
Hey.
How's your date?
Not so good.
Oh. So much for Jake's
lucky condom, huh?
Yeah, we never got
to condoms.
She thinks I'm still too
hung up on Bridget.
No kidding.
And the worst part is
Bridget agrees with her.
Well, I might as well put
my ring back on.
You, uh, you, uh, want-want
your ring back?
Yeah.
Here.
Thanks.
I had a feeling sooner
or later you'd want it.
No. You know what?
I was right the first time.
I don't need this anymore.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
I feel better already.
Oh, good.
All right, I'm gonna
go inside.
Okay, I'm just, I'm just
gonna hang here for a while.
Okay. Good night.
Yeah. Night.
My precious! My precious!
My precious!
You saw that?
Yeah.
Probably wondering what it was
all about.
Kinda.
Well... I often enjoy
a, uh, brisk moonlight swim.
Fully clothed?
You leave your clothes on
the beach,
a drifter... steals 'em.
Alan...
I was trying to get
your ring back.
But I don't want it back.
No, not-not for you.
Um, for me.
I was gonna pawn it.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
I need money.
I can't possibly produce enough
sperm and blood
to get out of the hole I'm in.
In fact, I went to the pawn shop
while you were on your date.
But you didn't pawn it.
I couldn't.
Wow, you must have been
freaking out
when I threw it
in the ocean, huh?
The truth of that stands
dripping before you.
Listen, if you
needed money,
why didn't you just ask?
You'd lend me money
if I just asked?
No. I don't believe in
lending money.
I just give it away.
Give it away?
Yeah, I think it's a bad idea
to lend people money.
They never pay you back,
and then you just end up
resenting them.
So how much do you need?
Uh...
No, no, I can't, I can't
take your money.
What, you're too proud?
Oh, God, no, I-I-I
haven't had any pride
since the gym showers
in seventh grade.
No, no, if I took your money,
that would change
our relationship,
and I don't want that.
I want you to think of me as
a friend and not a freeloader.
You don't think that ship's
already sailed?
Allow me at least
the illusion of self-respect.
Would it help your self-respect
if I started charging you rent?
Actually, it would.
Consider it done.
Great.
Oh, I'm gonna be late
this month.
No problem.
Probably next month, too.
Thanks for the heads up.
Okay. I guess I better
go dry off.
Hey, Alan.
Yeah?
You're a quality guy.
Really?
I have a lot of people that
say they're my friend,
but you really are one.
Well, thanks.
Just-just out of curiosity,
if I had asked for, say,
a hundred thousand dollars,
would you have given it to me?
Absolutely.
Where you going?
Back in the ocean.
Hello?
Oh, hey, Jake.
No, your dad's kind of busy
right now.
What's up?
Oh, you used the
frequent flier miles?
That's great.
Where are you?
I have no idea.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪